Guide to the Partners for Livable Communities collection, 1962-1994
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 5: Design, 1962-1989; (6.5 boxes)
  - Architecture of monuments: the Franklin Delano Roosevelt Memorial Competition, 1962 (Box 17, Volume 4)
    Thomas H. Creighton
  - Architecture plus. Vol. 2, no. 2 (Mar./Apr. 1974) (Box 17, Volume 5)
  - Architecture quarterly. Introductory issue, 1984 (Box 17, Volume 6)
  - Arlington sign sense: Arlington, Mass., 1977 (Box 17, Volume 7)
  - Arts on the line: design quality in transit: prepared for the third annual meeting of Partners for Livable Places ..., 1980 (Box 17, Volume 8)
    Andrew Hyde
  - Australian built: a photographic exhibition of recent Austrialian architecture, 1985 (Box 17, Volume 9)
    Michael Griggs
  - Berlin building review '78, 1978 (Box 17, Volume 10)
  - Berlin building review '80, 1980 (Box 17, Volume 11)
  - Better place to live: new designs for tomorrow's communities, 1981 (Box 17, Volume 12)
    Michael N. Corbett
  - Briefings on development: an action guide. Vol. I, 1978 (Box 17, Volume 13)
    PACE
  - Briefings on development: an action guide. Vol. II, 1978 (Box 17, Volume 14)
  - Calgary builds: the emergence of an urban landscape, 1905-1914, 1985 (Box 18, Volume 1)
    Bryan P. Melnyk
  - Campana: Ingeniero White, puerto esperanza (selected clippings from La Nueva Provincia), 1984 (Box 18, Volume 2)
  - Changing Cities: an introduction to the economic and social research council inner cities research programme, 1985 (Box 18, Volume 3)
    Victor Hausner and Brian Robson
  - Chinese building standards in the 12th century, 1981 (Box 18, Volume 4)
    Else Glahn
  - Cities by design: an introduction for public administrators, 1984 (Box 18, Volume 5)
    Ronald L. Thomas,
  - Colorado Design Guidelines Project workbook #2, undated (Box 18, Volume 6)
    Barbara A. Cole
  - Commercial Intersections in Older Neighborhoods: New Orleans, 1980 (Box 18, Volume 7)
    Tulane School of Architecture
  - Concho, Arizona: A photographic study (scrapbook with captions), 1970 (Box 18, Volume 8)
    Willam H. Hunse, College of Architecture, Arizona State University
  - Controlling access in highrise buildings: approaches and guidelines: draft report, 1976 (Box 18, Volume 9)
    William Brill Associates
  - Design action. Vol. 1, no. 2 (Nov.-Dec. 1982) (Box 18, Volume 10)
  - Design Commission, 1971 (Box 18, Volume 11)
  - Design competitions, 1979 (Box 18, Volume 12)
    Paul D. Spreiregen,
  - Design guidelines: Mercer Island Design Commission, 1973 (Box 18, Volume 13)
    Joyce, Copeland, Vaughan & Nordfors, Jones & Jones
  - Designing against vandalism, 1983 (Box 18, Volume 14)
    James A. Wise
  - Designing our environment: artists + architects + people, 1978 (Box 18, Volume 15)
    University of Arkansas at Little Rock
  - Easton Design Guide, 1975 (Box 18, Volume 16)
  - EDRA 13: knowledge for design: proceedings of the 13th international conference of the Environmental Design Research Association ..., 1982 (Box 19, Volume 1)
  - Elements of Greek, Roman, and Gothic architecture: their influence on architectural development in western civilization, 1981 (Box 19, Volume 2)
  - Eye toward the future: factors to be considered in pedestrian designs, 1983 (Box 19, Volume 3)
    Michael John Pittas,
  - Form & purpose: is the emperor naked?, 1980 (Box 19, Volume 4)
    Moshe Safdie,
  - "Frederick Law Olmsted's Theory of Landscape Design", 1980 (Box 19, Volume 5)
    Charles E. Beveridge
  - Future of the piers: planning and design criteria for Brooklyn Piers 1-6, 1987 (Box 19, Volume 6)
    Buckhurst, Fish, Hutton, Katz
  - Gentle deterrent to vandalism, 1982 (Box 19, Volume 7)
    James A. Wise,
  - Guide to modern architecture, undated (Box 19, Volume 8)
    Royner Banham
  - Guide to the federal government for design and building professionals, 1981 (Box 19, Volume 9)
    John P. Eberhard
  - Improving the Design Quality of Federal Buildings., 1989 (Box 19, Volume 10)
  - Influence of the foreign heritage on the American city, 1976 (Box 19, Volume 11)
  - Inquiry by design: tools for environment-behavior research, 1981 (Box 19, Volume 12)
    John Zeisel,
  - Landscape architecture: a profession designed for minorities, undated (Box 19, Volume 13)
    A.S.L.A. Minority Recruitment Task Force
  - Lower Merrimack River valley: an inventory of historic engineering and industrial sites, 1976 (Box 19, Volume 14)
    Peter M. Molloy
  - Managing Design and Development, Vols 1-10, and Vol 25, 1981 (Box 20, Volume 1)
    various authors, National League of Cities
  - Matter of creation of the Office of the City Architect, April 6, 1988 (Box 20, Volume 2)
    San Diego City Council Committee on Rules, Legislation, and Intergovernmental Relations
  - Metal cornice: yesterday, today and tomorrow: implications for design and technology in urban housing conservation, 1985 (Box 20, Volume 3)
    Alan G. Levy
  - Milwaukee's Fountain Program: A project of the mayor's beautification committee, 1980 (Box 20, Volume 4)
    Loretta Johnson and Arlene Kennedy, committee chairs
  - Monumentum. Vol. 15-16 (1977): special issue devoted to the Conference on Vernacular Architecture, Plovdiv, Sept. 24-Oct. 2, 1975 (Box 20, Volume 5)
  - Neighborhood commercial district design guidelines, 1983 (Box 20, Volume 6)
    Wallace Rappe,
  - New directions in British architecture, 1968 (Box 20, Volume 7)
    Royston Landau
  - New directions in German architecture, 1968 (Box 20, Volume 8)
    Gunther Feuerstein
  - New directions in Italian architecture, 1968 (Box 20, Volume 9)
    Vittorio Gregotti
  - Old & new architecture design relationship: from a conference, 1981 (1st paperback ed.) (Box 20, Volume 10)
  - Oysterville architectural guidelines, 1979 (Box 20, Volume 11)
    Michael Parker
  - Parking lot landscaping, 1978 (Box 20, Volume 12)
    Margaret A. Corwin
  - Pedestrian city: a proposal for an American architecture and urbanism in the post-petroleum age, 1981 (Box 20, Volume 13)
    Roger C. Ferri
  - Pedestrian time-space concept: a new approach to the planning and design of pedestrian facilities, 1986 (Box 20, Volume 14)
    Gregory P. Benz
  - Perception and environment: foundations of urban design: proceedings of a 1962 seminar on urban design, 1966 (Box 21, Volume 1)
  - Places as Public Art, 1984 (Box 21, Volume 2)
    Diana Lands
  - Poble Sec: Notes per a la recuperacio d'un barri, undated (Box 21, Volume 3)
    Danial Navas
  - Policy development seminar on architecture, design and criminal justice, June 15-17, 1975, Rochester, Michigan (Box 21, Volume 4)
  - Practice of architectural control in northern Europe, 1968 (Box 21, Volume 5)
    Sidney Cohn
  - Public Interest No 74, Winter 1984: "Architecture and Public Spaces" (Box 21, Volume 6)
    Irving Kristol and Nathan Glazer, editors
  - Public Municipal and Community Buildings, 1980 (Box 21, Volume 7)
    Charles King Hoyt, AIA
  - Quality Without a Name: "Livability", ca. 1980 (Box 21, Volume 8)
    Joseph Grange
  - Rapport Preliminaire, 1983 (Box 21, Volume 9)
    Gerard Singer
  - Review of federal mandates related to environmental design and the quality of the built environment ..., 1978 (Box 21, Volume 10)
    Association for the Study of Man-Environment
  - Role of the Architect in Urban Development: International Conference, Strasbourg, 6-8 June 1984 (Box 21, Volume 11)
  - Role of the Architect in Urban Development: International Conference, unbound conference subthemes in French and English, 1984 (Box 22, Volume 1)
  - Romance with the city, Irwin S. Chanin, 1982 (Box 22, Volume 2)
    Diana Agrest
  - Rural architecture of central west Texas, 1840-1920: a study of indigneous architecture for National Endowment for the Arts, 1970 (Box 22, Volume 3)
    Mondel Rogers, Texas Tech University
  - SAR guide to contemporary Swedish architecture, 1968-78, 1978 (Box 22, Volume 4)
  - Selected articles on architecture in Chicago, 1976 (Box 22, Volume 5)
  - Six city sites: studies in contextual design, 1983 (Box 22, Volume 6)
    Alan Karchmer
  - Socio-environmental and aesthetic impact of tall buildings, 1985 (Box 22, Volume 7)
    H. Weese,
  - Sound wall design guide, 1979 (Box 22, Volume 8)
  - Space and Society: international journal of architecture and environmental design, no 27, 1984 (Box 22, Volume 9)
  - Study of visual, perceptual images of Ghirardelli and Union Squares in San Francisco, CA (Option A), 1971 (Box 22, Volume 10)
    Nancy B. Oleksa
  - Tall buildings, tight streets, 1984 (Box 22, Volume 11)
  - Tall buildings, tight streets: a research project, 1985 (Box 22, Volume 12)
  - Toward an Urban Design Manifesto, 1980 (Box 23, Volume 1)
    Donald Appleyard and Allan Jacobs
  - Urban design competitions, USA, 1985 (Box 23, Volume 2)
  - Urban structuring: studies of Alison & Peter Smithson, 1967 (Box 23, Volume 3)
  - Urbanization of suburbia: the renaissance of the row house, undated (Box 23, Volume 4)
    Dennis J. Dingemans
  - Vacant lottery, 1978 (Box 23, Volume 4)
    Barton Myers
  - Victorian commercial architecture in Indiana, 1978 (Box 23, Volume 5)
  - Water in design and nature, undated (Box 23, Volume 6)
    Craig Campbell
  - Westchester County policies on design and visual quality: county-owned properties and facilities, 1983 (Box 23, Volume 7)
  - Why buildings are known: a predictive tool for architects and planners, 1969 (Box 23, Volume 8)
    Donald Appleyard
- Series 6: Energy, 1975-1983; (2 boxes)
  This series contains numerous reports and studies on energy conservation planning as well as several congressional hearings on conservation policy. Most of the materials therein cover general issues (as opposed to case studies) including solar energy, bicycle transportation design, and making old buildings and historic districts energy efficient.
  - Assessing the energy conservation benefits of historic preservation: methods and examples, 1979 (Box 23, Volume 9)
  - Bicycle transportation for energy conservation: including a comprehensive bicycle transportation program, 1980 (Box 23, Volume 10)
    U.S. Department of Transportation
  - Block grant energy conservation, 1980 (Box 23, Volume 11)
    U.S. Office of Community Planning and Development
  - Community energy design primer, 1980 (Box 23, Volume 12)
  - Community energy design primer, 1980 (Box 23, Volume 13)
  - Compact cities: a neglected way of conserving energy: joint hearings ..., 1980 (Box 23, Volume 14)
    U.S. Congress. House. Committee on Banking, Finance ...
  - Compact cities: energy saving strategies for the eighties, 1980 (Box 23, Volume 15)
  - Controlling & managing energy boomtowns, 1979 (Box 24, Volume 1)
    Allan D. Garnaas
  - Davis energy book, 1981 (Box 24, Volume 2)
    Jerryne Philleo,
  - Designing an experimental solar community, 1977 (Box 24, Volume 3)
    Robert L. Thayer
  - Economic model for passive solar designs in commercial environments, 1980 (Box 24, Volume 4)
    Jeanne W. Powell
  - Energy and the city: hearings before the Subcommittee on the City ..., 1977 (Box 24, Volume 5)
    U.S. Congress House Committee on Banking, Finance and Urban Affairs
  - Energy-Conscious Development: options for land use and site planning regulations, Fairfax, VA, 1981 (Box 24, Volume 6)
  - Energy conservation and land development, 1977 (Box 24, Volume 7)
  - Energy conservation and solar energy for historic buildings: guidelines for appropriate designs, 1981 (Box 24, Volume 8)
    Thomas Vonier Associates
  - Energy conservation / Solar Training Institute: Permanent Facilities Planning Workshop, 1981 (Box 24, Volume 9)
    Congressional Research Service
  - Energy conserving site design: case study, the Woodlands, Texas: final report, 1980 (Box 24, Volume 10)
    Matt Swanson
  - Energy Expo '82, 1976 (Box 24, Volume 11)
  - Energy obesity: the deadly disease of a high-consumption society, 1980 (Box 24, Volume 12)
    Rufus E. Miles
  - Energy policy for the city: better services for less energy, 1979 (Box 24, Volume 13)
    Toronto, Ontario Commissioner of Planning and Development
  - Estimating transportation energy consumption of residential land types: final report, 1983 (Box 24, Volume 14)
    Dane County, Wisconsin Regional Planning Commission
  - Final report: energy conserving site design case study, Burke Center, Virginia, 1979 (Box 24, Volume 15)
    Land Design/Research, Inc.
  - Foresight Volume II: Energy Conservation in Cities, 1980 (Box 25, Volume 1)
    Subcommittee on Advanced Entergy Technologies...
  - Making Historic Districts Energy Efficient: A Case Study, 1982 (Box 25, Volume 2)
  - Master plan policies: St. Paul Energy Park, 1981 (Box 25, Volume 3)
    St. Paul, Minnesota
  - New energy from old buildings, 1981 (Box 25, Volume 4)
  - Planning land to conserve energy: 40 case studies from Canada and the United States, 1982 (Box 25, Volume 5)
    Reg Lang
  - Preservation and energy conservation, 1979 (Box 25, Volume 6)
  - Protecting solar access for residential development: a guidebook for planning officials, 1979 (Box 25, Volume 7)
    Martin Jaffe
  - Residential solar design review: a manual on community architectural controls and solar energy use, 1980 (Box 25, Volume 8)
  - Site planning for solar access: a guidebook for residential developers and site planners, 1979 (Box 25, Volume 9)
    Duncan Erley
  - Urban land policy: the energy problem and urban/regional planning in the 1980s: 26-30 Sept. 1981, Liege (Box 25, Volume 10)
- Series 7: Environment, 1970-1989; (3 boxes)
  This series contains plans and guidelines for environmental design and conservation in various regions including California, Delaware, northern Virginia, and Athens, Greece. The subjects covered include highway noise and beautification, rural land development, lake management, and water conservation.
  - Brookline: a guide to environmental design review, 1975 (Box 25, Volume 11)
  - California Tomorrow Plan, 1971 (Box 25, Volume 12)
    Alfred Heller, editor
  - County planning: how the English do it: report of an investigative workshop in England for ... Fauquier and Loudon Counties, Va., 1972 (Box 25, Volume 13)
  - Creative solutions to land development conflicts, 1981 (Box 25, Volume 14)
  - Cry California. Vol. 11, no. 3 (Summer 1976) (Box 25, Volume 15)
  - Delaware River basin: an environmental assessment of three centuries of change, 1975 (Box 25, Volume 16)
  - Design and development guidelines for San Diego, 1977 (Box 26, Volume 1)
    San Diego, California City Planning Department
  - Economics of noise expressway noise pollution abatement, 1975 (Box 26, Volume 2)
    Roger J. Vaughan and Larry Huckins
  - Effects of environmental amenities on patterns of economic development, 1980 (Box 26, Volume 3)
    Barbara A. Davis
  - Environment and community: a study in relationships based on the Hampshire/Romsey schools project, 1979 (Box 26, Volume 4)
    K. V. Bailey
  - Environmental Awareness Center: ten years in the upper Midwest, 1978 (Box 26, Volume 5)
    W. Thomas Lamm
  - Environmental conservation: a citizens' sourcebook, 1975 (Box 26, Volume 6)
    James H. M. Marshall
  - Environmental design: research and practice: proceedings of the EDRA 3/ar 8 Conference, University of California at Los Angeles ..., 1972 (Box 26, Volume 7)
    EDRA 3/ar 8 Conference (1972: UCLA)
  - Environmental quality and the built environment: notes prepared for presentation to the Fairfax County Environmental Quality Adv. Cn., 1981 (Box 26, Volume 8)
    D. Michael Murtha
  - Environmental report on noise abatement and control, 1980 (Box 26, Volume 9)
  - Environmentalism and real estate, 1981 (Box 26, Volume 10)
  - Forest We Live In: A special issue of American Forests, 1988 (Box 26, Volume 11)
  - Forestry, a community tradition, 1988 (Box 27, Volume 1)
  - Highway beautification: the environmental movement's greatest, 1979 (Box 27, Volume 2)
    Charles Floyd
  - Highway Noise, 1976 (Box 27, Volume 3)
  - Highway noise and compatible land use: case histories, 1979 (Box 27, Volume 4)
  - How to judge environmental planning for subdivisions: a citizen's guide, 1981 (Box 27, Volume 5)
    Perrin Stryker,
  - Interceptor sewers and suburban sprawl: the impact of contruction grants on residential land use: executive summary, 1974 (Box 27, Volume 6)
    Urban Systems Research & Engineering, Inc.
  - Lake management case study: Westlake Village, California, 1977 (Box 27, Volume 7)
    William A. Hanson
  - Land development in wooded areas, undated (Box 27, Volume 8)
    Gary A. Moll
  - Land Use Controls Annual, 1971 (Box 27, Volume 9)
  - Land use plan, Dane County, Wisconsin: a part of the master plan for Dane County, 1973 (Box 27, Volume 10)
  - Livable city, 1982 (Box 27, Volume 11)
    Joan Davidson
  - Managing strip development within the rural countryside, 1982 (Box 27, Volume 12)
    Robert A. Lambe
  - On the waterfront, 1981 (Box 27, Volume 13)
  - One space, many places: folklife and land use in New Jersey's Pinelands National Reserve ..., 1986 (Box 27, Volume 14)
    Mary Hufford
  - Pictorial atlas of the Netherlands, 1983 (2nd rev. ed.) (Box 27, Volume 15)
    State University of Utrecht
  - Plants, people, and environmental quality: a study of plants and their environmental functions, 1972 (Box 27, Volume 16)
    Gary O. Robinette
  - Potomac: a model estuary, 1970 (Box 27, Volume 17)
  - Protecting nature's estate: technique saving land / edited by Emily Jane Stover, 1975 (Box 27, Volume 18)
  - Rebirth of Athens: The Master Plan 1983; The anti-pollution program (Box 28, Volume 1)
    Ministry of Physical Planning, Housing, and the Environment; Athens, Greece
  - Reducing landslide hazards: a guide for planners, 1981 (Box 28, Volume 2)
  - Role of natural processes in the design of cities, 1980 (Box 28, Volume 3)
    Anne Whiston Spirn
  - Saving America's countryside: a guide to rural conservation, 1989 (Box 28, Volume 4)
    Samuel N. Stokes
  - Saving farms and farmlands: a community guide, 1978 (Box 28, Volume 5)
    William Toner
  - Tree city USA (pamphlets and memos on conservation), 1987 (Box 28, Volume 6)
  - Water conservation in residential development: land-use techniques, 1982 (Box 28, Volume 7)
    Welford Sanders
- Series 8: Handicap Accessibility, 1975-1980; (1 box)
  This series contains a small number of manuals on the incorporation of accessibility features into architecture and urban design.
  - Accent on access, 1975 (Box 28, Volume 8)
    Larry Kirk
  - Access to historic buildings for the disabled: suggestions for planning and implementation, 1980 (Box 28, Volume 9)
    Charles Parrott,
  - Access to play: design criteria for adaptation of exisiting playground equipment for use by handicapped children, 1979 (Box 28, Volume 10)
    Pittsburgh Architects Workshop
  - Accessibility modifications: guidelines for modifications to existing buildings for accessiblity to the handicapped, 1976 (Box 28, Volume 11)
    Ronald L. Mace
  - Accomodating the physically handicapped on over and undercrossing structures. 1, Feasibility study, undated (Box 28, Volume 12)
  - Accomodating the physically handicapped on over and undercrossing structures. 2, Guidelines, undated (Box 29, Volume 1)
  - Accomodating the physically handicapped on over and undercrossing structures. 3, Implementation manual, undated (Box 29, Volume 2)
  - Barrier-free design: report of a United Nations expert group meeting, 1975 (Box 29, Volume 3)
    Susan Hammerman and Barbara Duncan, editors
  - Mobile homes: alternative housing for the handicapped, undated (Box 29, Volume 4)
  - Play spaces to accommodate disabled children, 1980 (Box 29, Volume 5)
    James H. Melvin
- Series 9: Open Spaces, Parks, and Recreation, 1971-1990; (3 boxes)
  This series consists mostly of plans and reports on the design and development of open spaces, parks, and cultural facilities. The subjects addressed include urban open spaces, parks, zoos, waterfront revitalization, and urban forestry in such cities as Dayton, Pittsburgh, Camden, Chattanooga, San Francisco, and Tampa.
  - Abandoned Railroads in Maine, 1973 (Box 29, Volume 6)
  - America's coasts: progress & promise, 1985 (Box 29, Volume 7)
  - Architectural Records Article, 1981 (Box 29, Volume 8)
  - Bay Area: a study of urban open spaces, 1977 (Box 29, Volume 9)
    Kathryn Mathewson
  - Buffalo Waterfront Master Plan, 1985 (Box 29, Volume 10)
    Wallace Roberts and Todd
  - California Waterfront Age Vol. 1 No. 4, The San Francisco Bay, 1985 (Box 29, Volume 11)
    Donald B. Neuwirth, editor
  - Camden: US arts: strategies for the 80's, 1986 (Box 29, Volume 12)
  - Caution: Working Waterfront: the impact of change on marine enterprises, 1985 (Box 29, Volume 13)
    Ann Breen and Dick Rigby
  - Chattanooga Riverfront: preliminary site and economic evaluation, 1984 (Box 29, Volume 14)
    Carr, Lynch Associates, Inc.
  - City Waterfront: Ending an Era of Neglect, 1971 (Box 29, Volume 15)
  - Community Open Spaces: Greening neighborhoods through community action and land conservation, 1984 (Box 30, Volume 1)
    Mark Francis, Lisa Cashdan, and Lynn Paxson
  - Comparison of Urban Forest Management Systems in Milwaukee, Cincinnati and Dayton, 1982 (Box 30, Volume 2)
    Mollie K. Hughes
  - Consensus seeking for waterfront revitalization thorugh visual stimulation in Clayton, New York, undated (Box 30, Volume 3)
    Gary J. Willmott
  - Future of Urban Forestry, 1980 (Box 30, Volume 4)
    City of Dayton, Ohio
  - Illinois and Michigan Canal National Heritage Corridor Act of 1984 (Box 30, Volume 5)
  - Implications of the Citizen Greenbelt Proposal, 1985 (Box 30, Volume 6)
    Bay Area Greenbelt Congress, San Francisco
  - Is South Street Seaport on the Right Tack?, 1981 (Box 30, Volume 7)
    Patricia Leigh Brown
  - Low-cost improvement of the outdoor environment of urban areas, 1976 (Box 30, Volume 8)
    Organization for Economic Cooperation and Development
  - MacArthur Park Design Guidelines, undated (Box 30, Volume 9)
    Barbara Goldstein, editor
  - Making of Neighborhood Open Spaces, 1981 (Box 30, Volume 10)
  - Mosaic by the Sea: False Creek South Shore, a New Concept in Inner City Living, ca. 1980 (Box 30, Volume 11)
  - Planning for Wildlife in Cities and Suburbs, 1978 (Box 30, Volume 12)
    Daniel L. Leedy, Robert M. Maestro, etc.
  - Neighborhoods as Stands in the Urban Forest, 1984 (Box 30, Volume 13)
  - New York City Open Space Task Force, ca. 1980 (Box 30, Volume 14)
  - Olmsted Legacy of Public Design, 1981 (Box 30, Volume 15)
    Charles E. Beveridge, editor
  - Open Space and the Built Environment: Testimony of U.S. House of Representatives Committee on Interior and Insular Affairs, 1990 (Box 30, Volume 16)
    Randolph McAusland, Director, Design Arts Program, NEA
  - Outdoor Advertising Control Program Needs to be Reassessed: Report to the Chairman, Committee on Environmental and Public Works, 1985 (Box 30, Volume 17)
    Comptroller General
  - Pennsylvania Heritage Parks: a concept with applications, 1984 (Box 30, Volume 18)
    Continuous Recreation Planning Program, U.S. Department of Interior
  - Pittsburgh's Downtown Open Spaces, 1982 (Box 30, Volume 19)
    Pittsburgh Department of City Planning
  - Principles of Landscape Design, 1975 (Box 30, Volume 20)
    Leon County Board of County Commissioners
  - Private Urban Open Space Development: Thesis Project Report Presented to the Faculty of California Polytechnic State University, 1980 (Box 30, Volume 21)
    James William Harvey
  - Regulating Videogames, 1982 (Box 30, Volume 22)
  - Reid Park Zoo, Master plan & exhibit development program, ca. 1981 (Box 30, Volume 23)
    Design Research Consultants
  - Reid Park Zoo, Research and Design at, ca. 1981 (Box 30, Volume 24)
  - Reid Park Zoo, Supplemental Research Results, ca. 1981 (Box 30, Volume 25)
  - Rutgers Camden Music Festival, 1988 (Box 30, Volume 26)